## Kendall Clark // UX Designer

213-399-3200

kendallclarkdev@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://kendallclarkdev.github.io/Kendall-Clark-portfolio/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kendallclarkdev/

#### **SUMMARY**

Hello!! I'm a Ux/UI Designer with a talent for making User-centered Designs from Phone Apps to web pages. With a strong knowledge of User Research and Prototyping as well As Building/Coding. I am very communicative and team-oriented with proficiency in HTML/CSS/JS with a Proven history of fostering Planning and design to meet team, individual and management objectives.

### **SKILLS AND TOOLS**

**Skills**: User Interface Design, UX Design, Interaction Design, UX Research, Graphic Design, Prototyping, Motion Design, Wireframing, User Interviews, Affinity Mapping, Responsive Web Design, Content Creation, Card Sorting, Usability Testing

**Tools:** Adobe Suite, CSS, Elementor, Figma, Figjam, Google Suite, HTML, Sketch, Mural, Miro, Invision, Principle, Trello, Notion, Sketch, Slack, Wix, Webflow, WordPress

## **RELEVANT EXPERIENCE**

#### **UX** Lead

## Genius Diagnostics // Mobile A.I. Phone App

An app that Allow users to track symptoms of chronic fatigue syndrome With Artificial intelligence Length: 10/2021 - 11/2021

- Lead design sprints, ideating user-centered design decisions, synthesizing user data balancing user and stakeholder needs
- Worked collaboratively with a product manager, and team to plan, create, and communicate effective interface designs
- Created user flows, sketches, wireframes, high fidelity mockups, wireflows, and high fidelity prototype designs recommendations and deliverables for client
- Presented and communicated designs and design goals to teammates, clients, and leadership
- Conducted research on VR health and Tech companies
- Translated UX vision into clear and meaningful user stories
- Communicated complex designs to both technical and non-technical team members

## **UI Lead Designer**

### Career Carrot // Saas Mobile Web App

Career Carrot An App that helps DC residents explore pathways and plan a course to pursue new careers.

Length: 10/2021 - 11/2021

- Designing page layouts, style guides, images, icons, and animations
- Work with tools including Adobe Suite, Google Workspace, WordPress, HTML, CSS, and JS
- Oversees the translation of design from concept through implementation
- Collaborating and communicating regularly with team
- Ensures final product adheres to UX standards
- Prepare and organize content and marketing material
- Optimize content to search engine criteria

# Front-End Web Developer Domecity tv (Podcast) // Landing Website

Design a Website For a Podcast / Media Company

Length: 08/2021 - 09/2021

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Ensuring user experience determines design choices.
- Developing features to enhance the user experience.
- Striking a balance between functional and aesthetic design.
- Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones.
- Building reusable code for future use.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Utilizing a variety of markup languages to write web pages.
- Maintaining brand consistency throughout the design.

## **EDUCATION**

## Team Treehouse | Remote

Front-End Developer Certificate

## General Assembly | Los Angeles, CA

User Experience Design : Ux/UI Design

Completed Nov 2021